[{"question":" How can you open a file selected in Lightroom CC for retouching in Photoshop CC?","options":[{"text":"Double-click the file","correct":false},{"text":"Choose File > Edit in Photoshop","correct":true},{"text":"Choose File > Save to Photoshop","correct":false},{"text":"Press Cmd/Ctrl+E","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" How can you undo one or more changes just made to an image?","options":[{"text":"Use the keyboard shortcut Cmd/Ctrl+Z","correct":false},{"text":"Click a state in the history panel","correct":true},{"text":"Choose File > Undo","correct":false},{"text":"Press Cmd/Ctrl+U","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" How can you select a specific layer? (find all that apply)","options":[{"text":"Click the eye icon in the layers panel","correct":false},{"text":"Use the Move tool with auto-select enabled","correct":true},{"text":"Right-click the image and select layer","correct":false},{"text":"Press Cmd/Ctrl and click the layer","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" How can you avoid having transparent edges along the edge of a panoramic photo while retaining the largest image size?","options":[{"text":"Choose the Cylindrical method.","correct":false},{"text":"Choose the Perspective method.","correct":false},{"text":"Adjust the Boundary Warp slider.","correct":false},{"text":"Select Auto Crop.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" How do you crop a document without permanently discarding pixels along the edge?","options":[{"text":"Clear the Delete Cropped Pixels box.","correct":false},{"text":"Select the Delete Cropped Pixels box.","correct":false},{"text":"Use the Smart Crop tool.","correct":true},{"text":"Hold the Alt (Windows) or Option (Mac) key.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What feature should you use to simulate the in-camera development recipes applied by manufacturers with your own raw files?","options":[{"text":"presets","correct":false},{"text":"Camera Matching profiles","correct":true},{"text":"calibration","correct":false},{"text":"snapshots","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" When working in an RGB document, which option is **NOT** a method for the Select Color Range command?","options":[{"text":"Sampled Colors","correct":false},{"text":"Skin Tones","correct":false},{"text":"Key (Blacks)","correct":true},{"text":"Out of Gamut","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" How do you access the Auto Color Correction Options dialog box?","options":[{"text":"Select Image > Auto Tone.","correct":false},{"text":"Select Image > Auto Color.","correct":true},{"text":"Alt-click (Option-click) the Auto button in the Properties panel when you have a Levels or Curves adjustment layer targeted in the Layers panel.","correct":false},{"text":"Hold down the Alt (Option) key and select Image > Auto Color.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which options are available when using the Free Transform command on a Smart Object?","options":[{"text":"C,D","correct":false},{"text":"D,E","correct":false},{"text":"B,C","correct":true},{"text":"C,E","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is considered the minimum DPI for photographic-quality inkjet printing?","options":[{"text":"300","correct":true},{"text":"100","correct":false},{"text":"1,000","correct":false},{"text":"72","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which scanner type is capable of producing the highest resolution scans?","options":[{"text":"flatbed scanner","correct":true},{"text":"slide scanner","correct":false},{"text":"all-in-one unit","correct":false},{"text":"drum scanner","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which format does NOT support an alpha channel?","options":[{"text":"PSD","correct":false},{"text":"PNG","correct":true},{"text":"TIFF","correct":false},{"text":"BMP","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the best way to save multiple images into a single PDF?","options":[{"text":"Save each PDF separately first and then combine them.","correct":false},{"text":"Check to see if you have Acrobat Professional installed.","correct":false},{"text":"Use the PDF Presentation command.","correct":true},{"text":"Click File > Export > Export Layers to Files.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What option cannot be adjusted with the Print command directly in the Print window?","options":[{"text":"size of the image","correct":false},{"text":"position on the page","correct":false},{"text":"paper quality","correct":true},{"text":"color management policies","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement best describes the Quick Mask feature?","options":[{"text":"It allows you to use the Pen tool to edit a selection","correct":false},{"text":"It allows you to use the Brush tool to create or refine a selection","correct":true},{"text":"It allows you to duplicate a mask quickly.","correct":false},{"text":"It allows you to convert a vector mask to a layer mask.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What Photoshop feature was used to convert this image to black and white?","options":[{"text":"Black and White adjustment layer","correct":false},{"text":"Posterize","correct":false},{"text":"Threshold","correct":true},{"text":"Image > Mode > Grayscale","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In the image shown, why is Sharpen Edges grayed out?","options":[{"text":"The filter doesn't work on a 16-bit image.","correct":false},{"text":"The filer is not correctly installed.","correct":false},{"text":"The filter doesn't work on a 32-bit image.","correct":false},{"text":"The filter requires a selection to be made first.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In the image shown, which Camera Raw feature was used to restrict the graduated filter to avoid the statue?","options":[{"text":"Adjustment Brush","correct":true},{"text":"Depth Range Mask","correct":false},{"text":"Luminance Range Mask","correct":false},{"text":"Color Range Mask","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What can you use to save a common crop size?","options":[{"text":"tool sets","correct":false},{"text":"preferences","correct":false},{"text":"modifier keys","correct":false},{"text":"tool presets","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which Camera Raw Transform method is being used in the example shown?","options":[{"text":"Guided","correct":true},{"text":"Vertical","correct":false},{"text":"Level","correct":false},{"text":"Full","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". To reduce the file size of a PDF, what should you do?","options":[{"text":"Upsample large images","correct":false},{"text":"Convert 8-bit images to 16-bit","correct":false},{"text":"Apply compression to the document","correct":true},{"text":"all of these answers","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which image adjustment is **not** available as an adjustment layer?","options":[{"text":"Levels","correct":false},{"text":"Shadows/Highlights","correct":true},{"text":"Curves","correct":false},{"text":"Hue/Saturation","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". With default Essentials settings, where would you find the Red Eye tool?","options":[{"text":"grouped with the Eyedropper tool","correct":false},{"text":"Image > Mode > Red Eye","correct":false},{"text":"Edit > Red Eye","correct":false},{"text":"grouped with the Spot Healing Brush tool","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which option was **not** selected in the Magic Wand tool to create a selection like the one shown below?","options":[{"text":"Contiguous","correct":true},{"text":"Anti-alias","correct":false},{"text":"Auto-Enhance","correct":false},{"text":"Sample All Layers","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Where should you click to open a dialog box in which you can then choose to open a raw file as a Smart Object?","options":[{"text":"A","correct":false},{"text":"B","correct":false},{"text":"C","correct":true},{"text":"D","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which option would you use to clone while respecting perspective planes?","options":[{"text":"Patch","correct":false},{"text":"Vanishing Point","correct":true},{"text":"Clone Stamp","correct":false},{"text":"Healing Brush","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In order to run a filter on an entire video file, what must you do first?","options":[{"text":"Convert the video file to an image sequence.","correct":false},{"text":"Convert the video file to a Smart Object.","correct":true},{"text":"Actually, you cannot use filters on video files.","correct":false},{"text":"Convert the video file to an animated gif.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which file format does **not** support layers?","options":[{"text":"Photoshop EPS","correct":true},{"text":"Photoshop PDF","correct":false},{"text":"Large Document Format","correct":false},{"text":"Photoshop PSD","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Of these formats, which supports 16-bit images?","options":[{"text":"JPEG","correct":false},{"text":"GIF","correct":false},{"text":"PNG","correct":true},{"text":"Photoshop EPS","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What does the small black triangle in the lower-right corner of a tool indicate?","options":[{"text":"that the tool is currently deselected","correct":false},{"text":"tool options","correct":false},{"text":"that the tool is currently selected","correct":false},{"text":"grouped or hidden tools","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which command makes it easier to adjust selected areas of color in two images in order to make them similar?","options":[{"text":"Match Color","correct":false},{"text":"Replace Color","correct":false},{"text":"Hue/Saturation","correct":true},{"text":"Levels","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". If you scan a film or slide negative, which command turns it into a positive?","options":[{"text":"Reverse","correct":false},{"text":"Threshold","correct":false},{"text":"Invert","correct":true},{"text":"Inverse","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". A filter recipe can be saved as an action and set to your desktop for drag-and-drop usage by converting the filter recipe into a `___`.","options":[{"text":"droplet","correct":true},{"text":"batch","correct":false},{"text":"scriptlet","correct":false},{"text":"image process","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which tool is not found in the Select and Mask taskspace?","options":[{"text":"Refine Edge","correct":false},{"text":"Quick Select","correct":false},{"text":"Magic Wand","correct":true},{"text":"Lasso","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". To use blending modes with a filter, choose the `___` command.","options":[{"text":"Mix","correct":false},{"text":"Fade","correct":false},{"text":"Smooth","correct":false},{"text":"Blend","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which image adjustment is optimized for 32-bit images?","options":[{"text":"Exposure","correct":false},{"text":"Color Lookup","correct":true},{"text":"Brightness/Contrast","correct":false},{"text":"Curves","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". To hide the white borders around pixels that are viewed at a high magnification, which option do you disable?","options":[{"text":"Window > Workspace > Grid","correct":false},{"text":"View > Show > Slices","correct":false},{"text":"View > Show > Selection Edges","correct":false},{"text":"View > Show > Pixel Grid","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". To save a panel layout arrangement, what should you create?","options":[{"text":"A tool set","correct":false},{"text":"A layer set","correct":false},{"text":"A keyboard shortcut","correct":false},{"text":"A workspace","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which filter should you use to create photorealistic blurs?","options":[{"text":"Gaussian Blur","correct":false},{"text":"Lens Blur","correct":true},{"text":"Shape Blur","correct":false},{"text":"Surface Blur","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". When using the Type tool, what do you call the space between lines?","options":[{"text":"Vertical scale","correct":true},{"text":"Kerning","correct":false},{"text":"Leading","correct":false},{"text":"Tracking","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". If you want the most control over color when inkjet printing, which option should you select?","options":[{"text":"Color Handling: Photoshop Manages Colors","correct":true},{"text":"Separations","correct":false},{"text":"Color Handling: Printer Manages Colors","correct":false},{"text":"Hard Proofing","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You have an RGB image that you want to convert to a duotone, but in the image > Mode menu, the Duotone option in grayed out. Why is this happening?","options":[{"text":"You must add a spot color channel first","correct":false},{"text":"You must remove all existing color by Image > Adjustments > Desaturate first","correct":false},{"text":"Duotones require a single channel, so you must convert to grayscale first","correct":true},{"text":"Duotones require two channels, so you must delete one of RGB channels in the Channels panel first","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". For smoother, curved edges on a selection, be sure to enable the `___` option.","options":[{"text":"anti-alias","correct":true},{"text":"fade","correct":false},{"text":"blend","correct":false},{"text":"curve","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which web-ready format supports transparency and is optimized for continuous tone images such as photos?","options":[{"text":"GIF","correct":false},{"text":"PNG-8","correct":false},{"text":"PNG-24","correct":true},{"text":"JPEG","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You're trying to use the Healing Brush tool, but don't see results. What is the problem?","options":[{"text":"You forgot to Shift-click to set the source point for the tool","correct":true},{"text":"You forgot to Alt-click (Windows) or Option-click (Mac) to set the source point for the tool","correct":false},{"text":"You forgot to double-click to set the source point for the tool","correct":false},{"text":"You forgot to Ctrl-click (Windows) or Command-click (Mac) to set the source point for the tool","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which color space is best for web graphics?","options":[{"text":"Adobe RGB","correct":false},{"text":"ProPhoto RGB","correct":false},{"text":"RGB","correct":false},{"text":"sRGB","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which option do you use with the Dodge and Burn tools to prevent unwanted color changes like those shown in the image?","options":[{"text":"Sample All Layers","correct":false},{"text":"Protect Tones","correct":false},{"text":"Use Pressure for Size","correct":false},{"text":"Protect Colors","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which command in the **Smart Objects** submenu would you see to save the original file for the selected layer?","options":[{"text":"Edit Contents","correct":false},{"text":"Replace Contents","correct":false},{"text":"Relink to File","correct":false},{"text":"Export Contents","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In the image shown, which Blur method is being used to control focus with a series of pins?","options":[{"text":"Path Blur","correct":false},{"text":"Tilt-Shift Blur","correct":false},{"text":"Iris Blur","correct":false},{"text":"Field Blur","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In the image shown, what do the blue areas represent?","options":[{"text":"Color cast","correct":false},{"text":"Clipped shadow detail","correct":false},{"text":"Overexposed details","correct":true},{"text":"Clipped highlight detail","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What does the grayscale image in this figure show?","options":[{"text":"the edges affected by the Sharpen command as refined by the Masking slider","correct":false},{"text":"the edges affected by the Sharpen command as refined by the Radius slider","correct":false},{"text":"the edges affected by the Sharpen command as refined by the Detail slider","correct":false},{"text":"the edges affected by the Sharpen command as refined by the Amount slider","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Where do you click to adjust the blending mode for a Smart Filter?","options":[{"text":"A","correct":false},{"text":"C","correct":false},{"text":"D","correct":true},{"text":"B","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Where do you click to adjust the blending mode for a Smart Filter?","options":[{"text":"Photoshop does not have natural media brushes.","correct":false},{"text":"In the **Brushes** panel, select a brush and then select **Convert to natural media**.","correct":false},{"text":"In the **Brushes** panel, select **Legacy Brushes**.","correct":true},{"text":"in the **Tool Presents** panel.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""}]